Willard Mullin Cartoons
Willard Mullin Cartoons
1961-1966
Mullin, Willard, 1902-1978
2.5 linear ft.
240 original sports cartoons.
2651144
Biographical History
Willard Harlan Mullin (1902-1978) was an American sports cartoonist and illustrator.
Though born in the mid-west, Willard Mullin spent his formative years in Los Angeles, California, and it was there that he broke into the newspaper business as a staff artist for the Los Angeles Herald in 1923. In 1934, after brief stints with papers in Ft. Worth and San Antonio, Mullin landed with the New York World-Telegram and Sun where he would remain as sports cartoonist for the bulk of his career. Mullin was highly influential and is often cited as a major influence on many of the great sports cartoonists of the following generation, including Karl Hubenthal and Gene Basset. Mullin's career spanned a legendary era in New York sports history, and his images of the great Yankees teams, the Brooklyn Dodgers, the New York Giants and Mets are iconic. Possibly, Mullin's most famous creation was the "Brooklyn Bum"—a colorful Dodger fanatic who later followed the franchise west—but he was also noted for his "Mets kid" and "St. Louis Swifty" characters, as well as and his skillful renderings of animals and other team mascots. When the World-Telegram and Sun folded in 1966, Mullin continued doing freelance work, publishing sports illustrations and cartoons in The Sporting News, the Saturday Evening Post and Life, among many others. Willard Mullin received the National Cartoonist Society's prestigious Reuben Award in 1954 and the NCS award for Sports Cartoons eight times (1957-1962, 1964, 1965). In 1971, the NCS named him "Sports Cartoonist of the Century".
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Willard Mullin Cartoons collection contains 240 original sports cartoons from the early to mid 1960s. Most of the cartoons deal with New York sports topics including Yankees baseball, Giants and Jets football, the Mets, Madison Square Garden events and horse racing. There are a substantial number of cartoons dealing with boxing, especially the Cassius Clay/Sonny Liston fights of 1964 and 1965. The many New York Yankees cartoons in the collection are particularly representative of the team's 1964 campaign with Yogi Berra as manager, usually noted as the end of the great Yankees dynasty. There are many appearances of the Brooklyn Bum, the Mets kid, the St. Louis Swifty, and many other stock characters and animal mascots.
As the cartoons are not specifically dated, dates listed in inventory are derived from context. Original cartoon: traces of graphite, crayon, zipatone, brush, pen and ink on illustration board, approx. 15 x 22 in.
Arrangement of the Collection
Cartoons are arranged by sport and sorted in alphabetical order by title (or prominent caption, if untitled).
Related Material
has collections of over one hundred cartoonists. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Mullin, Willard, 1902-1978.; New York world-telegram and the sun.; Art -- Cartoonists.; American wit and humor, Pictorial.; Caricatures and cartoons -- United States.; Cartoonists -- United States.; New York Yankees (Baseball team) -- History -- Pictorial works.; Sports -- Caricatures and cartoons.; United States -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Cartoons (humorous images); Cartoonists.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on this material.
Acquisition Information
M12-071 ("...And with three straight Giants losses..."), purchase, 2012.
Inventory
*text in brackets taken from prominent caption.
- Baseball cartoons, 84
  - Advice From The Lovelorn, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Casey Stengel, Mets kid, Mets fans (Box 1)
  - [A.L. Pitching Averages…], 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Twins (Box 1)
  - All The Answers, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, George Weiss (Box 1)
  - Allegro, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Phillies, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Among The Missing, 1966; key words: Yankees, Red Sox, Mickey Mantle (Box 1)
  - Anchors Aweigh, 1965; key words: Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - …And So To Baltimore, 1966; key words: Dodgers, Orioles, Brooklyn Bum, oriole, 1966 World Series (Box 1)
  - …And With Three Straight Giants Losses..., key words: Giants, New York, barbershop, Sam Maglie (Box 1)
  - The Antidote?, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Athletics, Kansas City, "kissing cousin" (Box 1)
  - Balk!, 1961-1966; key words: Ford Frick, umpires, balk rule, Warren Giles, National League (Box 1)
  - The Best Team I Ever Had', 1965; key words: Yankees, Johnny Keane, Cardinals, St. Louis Swifty, 1965 season (Box 1)
  - Betsy Ross; Circa 1964, key words: Yankees, Yogi Berra, Ralph Hauk, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - Big Boy Now, 1961-1966; key words: Phillies, Bob Carpenter (Box 1)
  - [The Big Hearted N.L. Has A New Plan…], 1961-1966; key words: National League, Warren Giles, labor issues, Mets kid, Colt .45s cowboy, Yankee player (Box 1)
  - Bird Watcher, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Orioles, oriole (Box 1)
  - A Bit Warm For A Blanket, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, White Sox, Red Sox, Orioles, Kansas City Athletics, A.L. 1st division (Box 1)
  - Bombs Away, 1964; key words: Yankees, Yogi Berra, Ralph Hauk, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - [By A Strange Coincidence The Kansas City Athletics…], 1961-1966; key words: Charles O. Finley, Athletics, Kansas City (Box 1)
  - Cinderella…., 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Wes Westrum, Dick Stuart, Marv Throneberry, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - The Compact Job, 1964; key words: Yankees, Yogi Berra, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - The Company He Keeps, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Giants, Dodgers, Brooklyn Bum, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Easter Egg Hunt, 1961-1966; key words: Al Lopez, White Sox, Yankees (Box 1)
  - Enter The Patsy, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Giants, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Even Split, 1964; key words: Yankees, Cardinals, St. Louis Swifty, 1964 World Series (Box 1)
  - Flagpole?, 1961-1966; key words: Frank Robinson, Orioles (Box 1)
  - Gilled!, 1961-1966; key words: Gil Hodges, Senators, Yankees (Box 1)
  - Goin' My Way?, 1964; key words: Yankees, Mets, Mets kid, spring training (Box 1)
  - Good Enough Ain't Enough, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Pirates, Don Cardwell, Mets kid, pirate, "5 errors" (Box 1)
  - Hold That Tiger, 1963; key words: Yankees, Tigers, tiger (Box 1)
  - Home Is The Hero, 1964; key words: Yankees, cab ride (Box 1)
  - Home Coming, 1965; key words: Yankees, Johnny Keane, Twins (Box 1)
  - The Homefires, 1961-1966; key words: Mets fans, radio (Box 1)
  - How-Do, Again…, 1965; key words: Dodgers, Twins, Brooklyn Bum, Willard Mullin, 1965 World Series (Box 1)
  - [It Would Be Our Guess That Old Adage…], 1961-1966; key words: American League playoff picture (Box 1)
  - Jingle Bells, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Twins, snowball (Box 1)
  - Manna From Heaven, 1961-1966; key words: Fred Reichardt, Angels, Yankees (Box 1)
  - [The Mets Went Into The Pirates' Den…], 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Pirates, Mets kid, pirate (Box 1)
  - [The Mets Will Never Forget Their Finest Hour…], 1961-1966; key words: Billy Williams, Mets, Cubs, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Monkey Business, 1961-1966; key words: Dodgers, Brooklyn Bum, Walter O'Malley, Walt Alston, Buzz Bavasi, Charlie Dressen, Leo Durocher (Box 1)
  - Nail Everything Down!, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Braves, Native American figure, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - The 'New Breed'?, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Braves, Native American figure, Mets kid, "Boston-Milwaukee-Atlanta-wither-so-ever Braves" (Box 1)
  - Next Course!, 1966; key words: Mets, Reds, Opening Day 1966 (Box 1)
  - Non-Objective Painting, 1961-1966; key words: Charles O. Finley, Athletics, Kansas City, American League (Box 1)
  - Not His Dish, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, spring training, Grapefruit League (Box 1)
  - [Now Is The Time For The General Managers…], 1961-1966; key words: N.L. and A.L. presidents (Box 1)
  - Off And Running…But Not Very Fast…, 1966; key words: Mets, Reds, Yankees, Tigers, Mets kid, tiger, Opening Day 1966 (Box 1)
  - Oh, Say Can You See, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Mets, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Ole!, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, White Sox, wild bull (Box 1)
  - On The Beam…, 1965; key words: Dodgers, Brooklyn Bum, 1965 World Series (Box 1)
  - Onward And Upward, 1965; key words: Yankees, Angels, angel (Box 1)
  - [Orioles 4 …], 1961-1966; key words: Yankee players looking up at A.L. results on scoreboard (Box 1)
  - [Our Little Guy Must Be Growing Up…], 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Mets kid, "Miss N.L. pennant" (Box 1)
  - The Pasty Eater, 1961-1966; key words: Phillies, Colt .45s (Houston), Cubs, Mets, Giants, colt, bear cub (Box 1)
  - Play-Mates, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Astros, Mets kid, Colt .45s cowboy (Box 1)
  - Playmates, 1961-1966; key words: Phillies, Giants, "Carpenter's kids" (Box 1)
  - Portrait Of A Self-Satisfied Gent, 1963; key words: Mickey Mantle, Joe Pepitone, All-Star Game (Box 1)
  - Put Out More Flags, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Mets, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Quiz Program, 1961-1966; key words: Alfonso Ramon Lopez, White Sox, Indians, Yankees (Box 1)
  - Recording Secretary, 1964; key words: Jim Bunning, Mets, Phillies, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Reunion In Cooperstown, 1966; key words: Casey Stengel, Baseball Hall of Fame, Babe Ruth, Ty Cobb, Lou Gehrig, Mel Ott, Walter Johnson (Box 1)
  - A Run On Sox, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - Show-Down, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Orioles, White Sox (Box 1)
  - [Since The Yankee Season Started…], 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, rain out (Box 1)
  - Stee-e-rike!, 1961-1966; key words: National League umpires (Box 1)
  - Stormy Weather, 1966; key words: Yankees, Tigers, Mets, Reds, Mets kid, Opening Day 1966 (Box 1)
  - [That The Yankees Win By Clobbering The Pretenders…], 1964; key words: Yankees, Orioles, Yogi Berra, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - There Are Some He'd Like To Skip, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - They Went That Way?, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, 6th place (Box 1)
  - Tim-b-e-r-r-r, 1961-1966; key words: Harmon Killebrew, Twins, Yankees (Box 1)
  - To The Rescue!, 1964; key words: Mets, Phillies, Mets kid, Phillies 1964 collapse (Box 1)
  - The Trophy, 1966; key words: Yankees, Mets, Mets kid, Mayor's Trophy Game 1966, Mayor Robert F. Wagner, Jr. (Box 1)
  - [Two New Boys With Different Problems], 1964; key words: Yogi Berra, Hank Bauer, Yankees, Orioles, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - Two-Week Vacation, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, travel agent (Box 1)
  - Up To His Old Tricks, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Cardinals, Mets kid, St. Louis Swifty (Box 1)
  - Watch The Birdie, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Orioles, oriole (Box 1)
  - What Agenda?, 1961-1966; key words: N.L. and A.L. presidents, Joint Major League Baseball Meetings (Box 1)
  - [When The Yankees Left Home Ten Days Ago…], 1964; key words: Yankees, Yogi Berra, flying carpet, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - Wins Are Where You Find 'Em, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - [With The First All-Star Thing In The Books…], 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Angels, angel (Box 1)
  - [The Yankees And Dodgers Have Taken Off…], 1961-1966; key words: Dodgers, Yankees, Brooklyn Bum (Box 1)
  - [The Yankees Were In First Place When…], 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - [Yankees, With a 4 Game Winning String…], 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Angels (Box 1)
  - You Can't Prove It In L.A., 1961-1966; key words: Mets, Cubs, Leo Durocher, bear cub (Box 1)
  - Young Man's Burden, 1961-1966; key words: Bobby Murcer, Yankees (Box 1)
- Basketball cartoons, 4
  - Dan Cupid In Spades, 1961-1966; key words: Knicks, Celtics, Ned Irish (Box 2)
  - Metropolitan Standoff…, 1961-1966; key words: NYU, Fordham, St. Francis, Manhattan, Pa Knickerbocker (Box 2)
  - Neighborhood Rumble, 1961-1966; key words: NYU, Fordham, St. Francis, Manhattan, Pa Knickerbocker (Box 2)
  - Not Enough To Go 'Round, 1961-1966; key words: NIT, NCAA Tournament (Box 2)
  - [Pre-Season Predictions…], 1961-1966; key words: NYU, Syracuse, Lou Rossini, NIT (Box 2)
- Boxing cartoons, 19
  - As Maine Goes…, 1965; key words: Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Lewiston (Maine) (Box 2)
  - Awsk 'Ennery, 1964; key words: Henry Cooper, Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Miami (Box 2)
  - [Everyone Within 400 Miles…], 1965; key words: Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Lewiston (Maine), Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - Feet Of Clay, 1961-1966; key words: Cassius Clay (Muhammad Ali), crumbled statue (Box 2)
  - The Foundling, 1965; key words: Lewiston (Maine), Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston (Box 2)
  - Hands Up!, 1966; key words: Cassius Clay, Ernie Terrell, Houston (Texas) (Box 2)
  - The Hat Trick, 1966; key words: Emile Griffith, Joey Archer, Dick Tiger (Box 2)
  - Hot Air, 1964; key words: Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Miami (Box 2)
  - The Kid Brother, 1961; key words: Floyd Patterson, Ingemar Johansson, Raymond Patterson (Box 2)
  - [The Only Thing We Really Don't Know…], 1966; key words: Cassius Clay, Cleveland Williams, Houston (Texas) (Box 2)
  - Q And A, 1965; key words: Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Lewiston (Maine), Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - [Richard Ihetu Is A Personable Young Man…], 1963; key words: Dick Tiger (Richard Ihetu), Joey Giardello, tiger (Box 2)
  - Shadow Boxers, 1965; key words: Zora Folley, Oscar Bonavena (Box 2)
  - Situation Normal, 1963; key words: Luis Rodriguez, Skeeter McClure, Knicks, Rangers, Madison Square Garden (Box 2)
  - Sonny Side Of The Street, 1963; key words: Floyd Patterson, Sonny Liston, Cassius Clay, Henry Cooper, Billy Daniels, Doug Jones (Box 2)
  - Target For Tonight, 1966; key words: Joey Archer, Emile Giffith (Box 2)
  - What'll Ya Bet?, 1963; key words: Floyd Patterson, Sonny Liston (Box 2)
  - Who's Fighting Whom?, 1964; key words: Cassius Clay (Box 2)
  - Who's Who, 1961-1966; key words: Willie Pastrano, Joey Giradello, Emile Griffith, Carlos Ortiz, Ultimino Ramos, Eder Jofre, Pone Kingpetch, Willard Mullin (Box 2)
- Football (College) cartoons, 26
  - All For One, 1966; key words: Notre Dame, Michigan State (Box 2)
  - Book Learnin', 1964; key words: Roger Staubach, Navy, Penn State (Box 2)
  - Bull In The China Shop, 1961-1966; key words: College bowl schedule (Box 2)
  - Cat Expert, 1961-1966; key words: Harvard, Yale, Ivy League (Box 2)
  - The Chosen Few, 1963; key words: Roger Staubach, Dick Butkus, Bob Brown, Scott Appleton, All-America team selections (Box 2)
  - For The "Tie", 1964; key words: Army, Navy, Roger Staubach, Wayne Hardin (Box 2)
  - Gotham Bowl, 1961; key words: Ron Bull, Merlin Olsen, Utah State, Baylor, Gotham Bowl (Box 2)
  - Imagined…Or For Real?, 1963; key words: Navy, Duke, Roger Staubach, devil, mid-shipmen (Box 2)
  - [The Ivy League This Year…], 1964; key words: Princeton, Ivy League, tiger (Box 2)
  - The Jolly Roger, 1961-1966; key words: Roger Staubach, Navy, Army (Box 2)
  - Kipling Was Right, 1966; key words: UCLA, Penn State, Syracuse, Pittsburgh (Box 2)
  - Lucullan Fare, 1961-1966; key words: Pro Football Draft (Box 2)
  - The Missing Pieces, 1964; key words: Syracuse, Army, Yankee Stadium, Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - [Oh, Sure We Know…], 1963; key words: West Virginia, Pittsburgh, mountaineer, panther (Box 2)
  - The Old Army Game, 1966; key words: Army, Navy, Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - [The Only Common Opponent…], 1963; key words: Pittsburgh, Army, panther (Box 2)
  - Operation Fountain Pen, 1961-1966; key words: College stars, NBC, CBS, Pro Football Draft (Box 2)
  - Pall Over Pasadena, 1966; key words: Notre Dame, Purdue, USC, Rose Bowl (Box 2)
  - Peregrine V. Pedestrian, 1961-1966; key words: Army, Air Force, falcon (Box 2)
  - Private Fight, 1963; key words: Illinois, Big Ten (Box 2)
  - Re-Run, 1964; key words: Roger Staubach, Carl Stichweh, North-South Game (Box 2)
  - R.I.P., 1965; key words: Army, Paul Dietzel, free substitution rule (Box 2)
  - [Saturday You Can Tune In…], 1964; key words: Utah, West Virginia, Liberty Bowl (Box 2)
  - Stone-Age Bunyan, 1965; key words: WAC, two platoon football, free substitution (Box 2)
  - Swing It, 1963; key words: Army, Navy, Cotton Bowl (Box 2)
  - The Vision Of Early Fall, 1963; key words: College All-Star Game (Box 2)
- Football (Pro) cartoons, 36
  - Added Starters, 1966; key words: Cardinals, Bears, Halloween (Box 2)
  - All Right! All Right!, 1961-1966; key words: Giants, Cardinals, Jets (Box 2)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1963; key words: Giants, Packers, Bears, Lions, Colts, bear, lion, colt (Box 2)
  - Ashes To Ashes…, 1964; key words: Giants, Browns (Box 2)
  - Bone Of Contention, 1964; key words: Giants, Steelers (Box 2)
  - A Day With The Patsies, 1966; key words: Giants, Jets (Box 2)
  - Don't Ask, 1966; key words: Giants, Cardinals (Box 2)
  - Double Feature, 1965; key words: Giants, Jets, Cowboys, Bills, gun fighter, Buffalo Bill (Box 2)
  - Enter Pro-Football, 1964; key words: Giants, Jets, Eagles, Mets kid (Box 2)
  - Fall Speed Ahead, 1961-1966; key words: Giants, training camp (Box 2)
  - Final-Final, 1963; key words: NFL/AFL All-Star games (Box 2)
  - Halp!, 1963; key words: Giants, Eagles, Steelers (Box 2)
  - Heavy, Heay…, 1961-1966; key words: Giants, Browns, Jim Brown (Box 2)
  - Home, Sweat Home, 1961-1966; key words: Jets (Box 2)
  - Homecoming, 1964; key words: Giants, Redskins, Sam Huff, Davis Cup, Dennis Ralston, Chuck McKinley, tennis (Box 2)
  - In His Hair, 1963; key words: Giants, Jets, Packers, Allie Sherman, Weeb Ewbank (Box 2)
  - Just Can't Wait, 1966; key words: Pro Football schedule (Box 2)
  - …Meanwhile Back At The Wrench, 1965; key words: Giants, Jets (Box 2)
  - Next!, 1966; key words: Giants, Redskins, Native American (Box 2)
  - Not Much Of A Santa Claus, 1966; key words: Giants, Cardinals, Santa Claus (Box 2)
  - O! What A Fall Was There…, 1966; key words: Giants, Steelers (Box 2)
  - Pigskin Diet, 1961-1966; key words: Jets, Bills, Joe Namath, buffalo (Box 2)
  - Poor Timing, 1961-1966; key words: Bears, Packers, 49'ers (Box 2)
  - Pur-r-r-r-r-r-r, 1963; key words: Giants, Eagles, Y.A. Tittle, Allie Sherman, eagle (Box 2)
  - The Raw Material, 1965; key words: Giants, Jets, Allie Sherman, Weeb Ewbank (Box 2)
  - Reward In Miami, 1961-1966; key words: Giants (Box 2)
  - Santa Claws!, 1963; key words: Giants, Bears, Y.A. Tittle, bear, NFL Championship (Box 2)
  - Season's Greetings, 1961-1966; key words: 4th Annual American Football Coaches All-American Game (Box 2)
  - Short Summer - Hot, But Short, 1961-1966; key words: Giants, Jets, exhibition season opens (Giants/Bears in Ithaca) (Box 2)
  - Silver-Lining Department, 1961-1966; key words: Giants, Jets (Box 2)
  - Super Bowl ($1,200,000.00 ), 1966; key words: Packers, Chiefs, Native American, Super Bowl (Box 2)
  - [Tell Me Not In Mournful Numbers…], 1961-1966; key words: Giants (Box 2)
  - Top Hand, 1961-1966; key words: Jets, Chargers, horse (Box 2)
  - Wheeling and Dealing, 1964; key words: Giants, Cardinals, St. Louis Swifty (Box 2)
  - The Wrecker, 1963; key words: Steelers, Giants, Bears (Box 2)
  - You Explain It, 1964; key words: Giants, Redskins, Cowboys, Cardinals, Jets (Box 2)
- Golf cartoons, 6
  - Bugged, 1963; key words: Sam Snead (Box 3)
  - The Congressional, 1961-1966; key words: The Congressional, tiger (Box 3)
  - Deep Drain The Cup, 1964; key words: Tony Lema (Box 3)
  - Deep Fill The Cup…, 1965; key words: Tony Lema, British Open (Box 3)
  - …The Gang's All Here, 1961-1966; key words: The Thunderbird, Pa Knickerbocker, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - I'm In The Rough, 1961-1966; key words: U.S. Open (Box 3)
- Hockey cartoons, 6
  - The Art Critic, 1961-1966; key words: Rangers, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Brothers Under The Skin, 1961-1966; key words: Rangers, hockey fans, The New Breed (Mets fan) (Box 3)
  - A Good Round Figure, 1961-1966; key words: Rangers (Box 3)
  - Hottest Thing On Ice, 1961-1966; key words: Rangers (Box 3)
  - Our Heroes, 1961-1966; key words: Rangers, sports writers (Box 3)
  - The Well Dressed Man, 1961-1966; key words: Rangers, Maple Leafs (Box 3)
- Horse Racing cartoons, 37
  - Art Critics, 1961-1966; key words: Speedy Scot, Realization Stakes, Frederick van Lennep, Ralph Baldwin, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - The Big Apple, 1961-1966; key words: Aqueduct, last race of the season (Box 3)
  - The Bird Watchers, 1961-1966; key words: Flamingo Stakes, Roman Brother, Northern Dancer, flamingo (Box 3)
  - Birds Of A Feather, 1961-1966; key words: Flamingo Stakes, Hail to All, Native Charger, Johnny Sellers (Box 3)
  - Bon Voyage, 1961-1966; key words: Kentucky Derby, No Robbery, John Graver (Box 3)
  - Cotton-Batting Candidates, 1961-1966; key words: Sadair, Bold Lad, Bill Winfrey, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Don't Bet On It, 1961-1966; key words: Kentucky Derby, Damascus, Willie Shoemaker, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Good Samaritan, 1961-1966; key words: Aqueduct takes its annual break (Box 3)
  - The Horse's Mouth, 1961-1966; key words: Bret Hanover, Richard Downing, Futurity Stakes, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - It Must Be Hay!, 1961-1966; key words: Aqueduct, Nelson Rockefeller, Bob Wagner (Box 3)
  - A Little Piece Of Real Estate…, 1961-1966; key words: Dapper Dan, Belmont Stakes (Box 3)
  - The Lock, 1961-1966; key words: Bret Hanover, Adios, Commodore Stakes, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Meeting Themselves Coming Back, 1961-1966; key words: Yonkers Raceway, harness racing (Box 3)
  - [Northern Dancer], 1961-1966; key words: Northern Dancer, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - [The NYRA Hangs Up An Extra...], 1961-1966; key words: Bob Ussery, Smart Deb, NYRA (Box 3)
  - …Off Whose Noose?, 1961-1966; key words: Cardigan Bay, International Stakes, Yonkers Raceway (Box 3)
  - [Old Timers Around Any Sports Beat…], 1961-1966; key words: Overtrick, Realization Stakes (Box 3)
  - Only Money, 1961-1966; key words: unclaimed winnings (Box 3)
  - Owner And Prop, 1961-1966; key words: Jaipur, Manuel Ycaza, Donut King, Gotham Stakes (Box 3)
  - Pegged Out, 1961-1966; key words: Manuel Ycaza, Iron Peg (Box 3)
  - Picture Horse, 1961-1966; key words: Kelso, Suburban Stakes (Box 3)
  - Right From The Horse's Mouth…, 1961-1966; key words: Kentucky Derby prospects, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Rolling Home…, 1961-1966; key words: Kelso, Brooklyn Stakes (Box 3)
  - Roosevelt Raceway, 1961-1966; key words: Roosevelt Raceway, Yonkers Raceway, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - The Runt, 1961-1966; key words: Roman Brother (Box 3)
  - A Salute, 1961-1966; key words: Flag Raiser, Bob Ussery, Preakness Stakes (Box 3)
  - Same Old Story, 1961-1966; key words: Off Track Betting, New York State government (Box 3)
  - The Shoe Fits, 1961-1966; key words: Willie Shoemaker, Bonjour, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - [Something Just Might Shake Out…], 1961-1966; key words: Wood Memorial Stakes (Box 3)
  - Tempus Fugit, 1961-1966; key words: Bowie Race Track (Maryland) season opens (Box 3)
  - [This Is The Day…], 1961-1966; key words: Roosevelt Raceway season opens (Box 3)
  - [This Week N.Y. Thoroughbreds…], 1961-1966; key words: Speedy Scot, Ralph Baldwin (Box 3)
  - Uniform Of The Day, 1961-1966; key words: end of the racing season (Box 3)
  - Voodoo a-la-Louisville, 1961-1966; key words: Damascus, Ruken, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - Who Ya Throwin' At?, 1961-1966; key words: Candy Spots, No Robbery, Never Bend, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - The Will And The Way, 1961-1966; key words: Bill Hartack, Bold Lad, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - [The Winningest Horse Now Active…], 1961-1966; key words: Theo Messidor, Willem Geersen, International Trot (Box 3)
- Track and Field cartoons, 9
  - The Badger Game, 1961-1966; key words: Bob Hayes, Sam Perry, Fordham, NYAC Meet (Box 3)
  - The Cat And His Canary, 1961-1966; key words: ICAAAA (IC4A) Indoor Meet, Harvard, Navy, Villanova, wildcat (Box 3)
  - [Despite The Royal Ukase…], 1961-1966; key words: AAU Championships, NCAA, sanctioned competition (Box 3)